Metal Cardbot Commentary!
Music, Dance, and Mega Trucker!
Hey guys! I'm Jun.
Now that you're all here,
let's watch another episode of Metal Cardbot together!
It's "Metal Cardbot Commentary" time!
Mega Trucker, setup!
I'm Mega Trucker!
I'm excited to meet all these fun new friends!
It's nice to see you, Mega Trucker!
Today, let's watch the story of
how I met Mega Trucker!
Shall we get started?
Save me, brave warrior!
Wahaha! It's no use crying now!
The world belongs to Vance, the Demon King!
Not so fast, Demon King Vance!
Is that Jun, the warrior?
What? How did he make his way through all of our troops?!
Looks like I'll have to teach him a lesson myself!
Take them on, Blue Cop!
Mr. Warrior!
Huh? Jun, since when did you become a warrior?
Something's strange here.
Huh? Strange, how?
I'm a real warrior that saved princess Anna!
Ahh... Princess Anna... one little kiss on this cheek too, please...
Wake up!
Hey, mom... good morning...
Hahahaha! Jun the warrior!
Like that'd ever happen!
At least I can dream...
A giant robot was spotted in a carpark under an overpass last night.
A giant robot?
Here is the black box recording that became a hot topic over the Internet.
According to an eyewitness, a dump truck approached when he and his friends were dancing...
T-That's...
Wow!~ I was on the news?
Was my dancing that good?!
Don't keep attracting attention, Mega Trucker!
Next time, I'll give them a real look at my amazing dancing skills!
The news is not "Mowtown's Got Talent"!
That's coming out of your paycheck!
Oh no, not again!
There's no mistaking it. That's Mega Trucker.
Is that right?
I told him over and over again to lay low and not attract the attention of the natives.
What are you going to do? This already has over a million views, it's gone viral!
He won't listen to me anyway.
We'll just have to seal him.
Seal him?
With the power of the Metal Breath, you can seal a Metal Cardbot inside a Metal Card.
In any case, I need to try to convince Mega Trucker once more.
Yeah, but to do that, we have to go find him first...
Jun. Do you think you could procure a large speaker?
A speaker?
I think I have an idea.
Don't you think this is too loud?!
It's not loud enough.
What's this?
That Blue Cop guy came up with something like that?
Haha! How about that, Mega Trucker?
How do you like me and Blue Cop's plan?
How did you come up with such a strange dance?
I guess it is hard to call that dancing...
This is great! Step on the gas and let's dance the night away!
Uhh... Thunderbolt Smash!
Thunderbolt Smaaaa-
Hahaha!
Blue Cop's slapstick humor really cracks me up!
It was my first time using the Metal Breath, so I wasn't familiar with it yet!
Jun, I'm okay! Just give me the next command!
Blue Cop, Burst Shot!
Burst Shot!
Great!
How about that?
Burst Shot sure packed a punch!
It was a pretty good plan,
I'll give you that.
Huh? It's weird to suddenly hear a compliment from you!
Megabolt...
Punch!!
How was that, everyone?
That was my first time succesfully sealing a Cardbot!
You have no idea how happy I was!
Now then, please look forward to the next "Metal Cardbot Commentary"!